[Music]
thank you
so what happened next yeah don't leave
us hanging [__]
so anyway after I got done shooting
basketball with the fellow black boys in
my neighborhood I went to the club right
and this girl was bouncing her fat
boobies up against my face so I did what
any normal guy would do and started
spanking her
what do you mean any normal guy
hey dudes do you want to hear a joke
I've been working on
hit it bro and it better be so funny
that I [__] my pants
okay the 19th Amendment
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's my green bro for you not only is
he the best thief on Earth but he's also
the number one class clown
what can I say I'm a machine
what what's so funny I don't get it
the 19th amendment is what give girls
the right to vote
hey that is pretty funny
you know Jacob sometimes you can be a
pretty silly dude
my name is manic
there you guys are
the teacher said the cheerleader tryouts
are about to begin Mendy's offering
people to watch her shake her stuff for
50 cents are you interested
um excuse me who invited the bitters
one more word like that mister and I
won't let you put your face between my
cheeks
that is disgusting
but Trevor aren't you kind of a [__]
yeah I have sex like that [__] but
society says that she's a stupid
prostitute because she's a girl however
when a man has some gagging on his balls
it's cool because he's a guy
so I'm gonna agree with Society here
because it works in my favor are you
freaking kidding me that's so sexist
Knuckles why are you hanging out with
these guys
haha that's such a woman take
Sonic Manic you too you're supposed to
be better than this
oh light and upsis it's only a joke
no it's not girls are stupid and they
give the contagious disease called
cooties
that's why I don't even hug my mom well
that and she hasn't been home for 12
years
Sonic and manic look there isn't that
the guys they tried to climb in your
bedroom window
is that the Oracle of delphias what's he
doing here
let's go see what he wants maybe he
needs help
hey little baby are you having a hard
time finding mommy and daddy you know I
can be your daddy come here I have a
lollipop too I mean lollipop ha ha but
it's not like you could tell the
difference you're too young get the [__]
over here see I have to climb over the
fence
Oracle what the [__] are you doing
oh Sonic my friend I finally found you
found us
I have grave news to share with you
you'll remember my evil clone that was
trapped inside my crystal ball
the one you shoved in your butthole like
stuffing in a Thanksgiving turkey
hey you don't know why he put it there
it pains me to say that he escaped again
uh so you're here looking for him good
man for a moment I thought you were
preying on kindergartners
no that is exactly why I'm here actually
but that's not what we should be
focusing on
My Doppelganger is out there and I'm not
sure I can defeat him alone when he
escaped he took my magic crystal ball
with him
if he took your crystal ball how will
you absorb him back
I don't know if I can
but Oracle when you disappear forever if
you guys stay separated for too long we
can't let the great Seer vanish that
would put the whole world in danger
I'm afraid it already is my friends
after he stole my crystal ball he fled
to the Sands of Egypt
[Music]
it would seem that his goal is to take
over the planet Earth
the very same way the evil doctor robot
nicked a Don Mobius
many years ago
if he grows too powerful I don't think I
can contain him
but if you can't that would mean
yes the chance of saving my life now is
slim but hope is not yet lost
meet me later at Olive Garden I'll be
there eating breadsticks since I'm
probably going to die tomorrow they
technically can't charge me
and so the sun sets on my first day as
Emperor and tomorrow it shall rise
foreign you're not going to get away
with this
you [__]
[Music]
care to repeat that
you heard what I said I am not going to
give you the sack this faction of making
me repeat myself
[Music]
when my wife finds out I didn't come
home for mac and cheese she'll call the
cops and your dead boy
oh I'm afraid that won't be happening
Captain
squeeze squeeze pick up I swear to God
in hell you better not be banging your
assistant at work again if you don't
pick up the phone right now we are
through Mr up [__]
you monster how dare you kill my beloved
sea sponge wife
I'll kill you I swear I will kill you
for all that you have done
how could you possibly hurt me more
you already wounded me more than you
could ever imagine
by playing with my heart
[Laughter]
looks like everyone's here are you all
ready to go
[Music]
we're way past ready Seer just send us
where we need to go and we'll do it
you got spunk kid I like that but let's
see how far that will get you
now then listen up remember your
training up old
and you will hopefully survive this
Sonic your super speed faster than
lightning can strike
Knuckles the Echidna your Mighty
strength that can shut her Stars
Sonia the Hedgehog that thing you do
where you can spin really fast
that I don't know the name of
and Mandela tour your ability to suck
balls
will probably help the team
[Music]
and Manic the Hedgehog with your ability
to
[Music]
and lastly most importantly of all
Bartleby
yeah we know I got a lot of money
can we just stop wasting time and get on
with this [__]
good luck hedgehogs your true purpose
and faith will keep you safe
Oh my Captain you ass is so red like two
shiny apples guess it's time to put a
cheesecake in your butt
stop right there you evil fiend
Sonic how how did you know I was here
what's going on
don't think you can play us like last
time you idiot we got the whole story
now untie Captain squeeze and give back
the crystal ball you blasted
doppelganger
Sonic wait you have to listen the Oracle
of delphius is it's okay Captain we
already know
yes they'll leave it to us [__] you're
just a gray sponge with a huge butt
no you have it all wrong this isn't a
look-alike this is the real Oracle of
delphius
what did he say
that can't be true
there's no way Oracle Say It Isn't So I
thought you were our [__] that always
got us out of jams not get us into the
sticky situations
what happened to you being our homeboy
from the hood
foreign
looks like my evil clone betrayed me I
paid him 14 whole dollars to keep his
mouth shut
yes you have discovered the truth it is
I the Oracle of delphias
but why would you want to rule the world
you're supposed to be the beacon of good
you're not meant to act black
I tried to be good for the longest time
I even hated all of you in the battle
against tyranny
then what changed I realized something
this world is already lost
people hurt each other and take from
each other already
and worst of all the TV show of Sonic
Underground is still canceled
is such a world even worth saving
no but that's exactly why this world
needs to be protected
there are kids out there scared and
shamed for like kings Sonic Underground
but they stay strong
because they hold hope in their hearts
because they know deep down that's Sonic
Underground will return eventually
because that is the best goddamn show
that will never never let anyone down so
you see Oracle we don't want you as an
enemy
the funny thing about that is
we don't often get to choose our enemies
[Music]
great grandfather Affair you're here
I will only ask once stay your hand
Oracle or face my wrath
well it's an honor to meet the Great
Sage of the echidnas what brings you
here
you know as well as I do this path you
are choosing to go down as a dangerous
one as a sage myself it's my big fat
duty to keep you on the right track
you think you have the right to preach
to me
that's right [__]
[Music]
damn it's like a battle between the
three legendary saw neem from Naruto
damn not cause your granddad sucks
foreign
s
detain him at once
he's outnumbered should we intervene
don't underestimate my great-grandfather
you guys the title of the Great Sage of
the goodness isn't given to just anybody
there's no way he'll be captured
that got me right now you sexy the
monsters
now do you see what happens when you
attempt to play Hero Great Sage I'll
make you an offer join me and help me
overthrow this planet there is sure to
be enough sex slaves for the two of us
perhaps if the world wasn't at stake I
would take you up on that offer but you
chose to attack my great grandson that I
will not forgive
Granddad get out of there yet gently a
hero Fight Hard my friends you are all
that stand in the way between this world
and certain destruction yo old menu or
cheeks are busting out your pants
no no
he's a Hermit he doesn't have many
visitors
great grandfather is there
[Music]
pisses you'll pay for that nobody hurts
my beach and gets away with it but me
foreign
[Music]
the Battle Is Lost I'm going to get you
to safety
wait barnably I think I know how we can
defeat him
well I can just go over there and punch
him
I'm in a way that one cause a tearing
time and Spice
then spitted out old man my friends are
dying out there the great magic of the
echidnas I wanted to give it to your
plump ass
but why I'm not enough I'm a mink
originally I wanted to transfer to my
great grandson one day but I feel he
lacks the potential you on the other
hand
that your hair is so perfect and you
smell like roses I couldn't imagine
anyone more deserving to carry on my
family's lineage
take up that staff there and all my
ancestors pars will flow into you
like when the Elemental Heroes had
beyond the burst in a tricks play man
and Bubble Man fuse together to create
Elemental Hero electrum
[Music]
s
I'm gonna kick your [__] ass boy
[__] he's got a gun
[__] it sounds like the fight's already
started
how the [__] are we going to get back up
there in time
Knuckles hey aren't you listening to me
don't you ignore me sausage head
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm ready to explore right up in the sky
I wish it didn't have to end this ways
here but you left me with no other
choice but to Buster cap in your ass
maybe next time you'll think twice about
not being a homes Killy G biscuit
now I'm going to blow your brains out as
Mexican people say sayonara
then go ahead and do it it should be
easy
especially for someone like you who once
already killed a friend
huh what do you mean by that I have
never done such a thing you are nothing
but a big fat liar you poopy head
is that so then take a look for yourself
[Music]
wait a minute that guy wasn't my friend
foreign
[Applause]
so what are you going to do now Captain
squeeze
I'm not sure the Oracle is [__] gone
and my house is caked in my wife's blood
I'll probably go to jail or some [__] so
I'm gonna move to the next state over
and pray to God that they don't catch
whiff of my right pass
honestly can I say something I am
honored that the will of my ancestors
will live on with any of all people
don't tell me you still haven't noticed
it yet
noticed what
simply put I never did use your power
here today are you saying that
everything you did was that's right all
me baby
you're wrong about your great-grandson
he isn't like Manic the Hedgehog he does
indeed have the potential you seek
while it may not be visible by the naked
eye he does have what it takes to make
you proud and to carry on the outkidna
on Legacy do you really think so
I know so just don't force anything upon
Him especially your own powers let him
choose his own path
but who wouldn't want to use my magic
well for one your magic is a gross
greenish yellow looking color like a
fart cloud
but that's what makes it sexy
it's only sexy to you
thank you barnably I think I can't stop
worrying though actually
[__] what is wrong the day is one
aren't you happy
Knuckles he's so far ahead of me
huh so that's what this is about
today's not the first time I noticed
it's happening time and time again
he's gotten so strong so fast how will I
ever be able to catch up to him at this
rate
it's like I can barely even see him
that's how much I've fallen behind
yo Beach you're so silly
what do I do
is it because I'm fat
[Music]
[__] listen to me today's victory was
all because of you
me but how how can that be so
it's simple because I saved us
I saved us because I only have one
person that I couldn't get out of my
mind do you know who that person is
you shouldn't worry about comparing
yourself to your friends because we all
bring something special and you bring
the cuteness and a huge [__] smelly
but crack
but if it will make you feel better meet
me at my condo at eight tonight for some
special training
thank you oh God I'm so tired is working
out really this hard
babe I am so pooped I changed my mind
can I have my chili dogs now
[Music]
I love we now
belong in this life
[Music]
no no no no no no no
beans
[Music]